What are we doing here?
What's the plan?
- Ask your brother.
- Wallah, what's he talking about?
Younes needs to be taught a lesson.
Are you kidding, wallah?
What do you mean a fucking lesson?
Younes is a fucking bitch.
I'm just gonna rough him up a little.
- So why did you bring a gun?
- In case he bolts, obviously.
Shut up. Saddam, start the car.
This guy is out of his mind. Saddam?
- Come on, just relax.
- Don't fucking touch me!
- What's your problem?
- Don't point that gun at me!
- Start the car. Let's get out of here.
- We're not going anywhere. Sit back.
We're on a stake-out,
and you're screaming and shouting.
- Hey! Stop yelling.
- Start this fucking car and let's go!
Hey, hey! Look.
A Christmas present, shababs.
- Yallah. Come on, get out!
- Cairo!
- Hey, Younes. Fucking bum.
- Cairo, what the fuck?
Shut up. Look at this.
Stay away from my clients.
Cairo, he's been taught his lesson.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
- You've taught him. Let's go.
- Fucking dog.
Amir! Amir!
Amir!
Saddam!
What the fuck are you doing?
- Amir. Amir, wake up.
- Cairo.
- Amir, wake up!
- Cairo, the police are coming.
- He fucking shot him. My brother.
- Hey! Cairo, look at me.
- Yallah. Listen to me. Let's go.
- It's my brother.
- We need to go. I've got you.
- Shut up, man! It's my fucking brother.
Are you out of your mind?
We gotta go! Cairo! Yallah!
Amir!
Amir... Amir!
10 YEARS LATER
CROSSING LINES
Gimme a drag.
You sure you're not pregnant?
- Just a drag.
- It's a slippery slope.
- I wish I were.
- Pregnant?
A little mini-you.
- Wouldn't that be fun?
- Sure...
Not you when you were young, though.
That would stress me out.
You have enough stress.
What would we call him?
I don't know. Got any suggestions?
- Muhammad! That's how we'd say it.
- That's how you'll call for him?
A little bundle of stress.
"Come here, Muhammad!"
Oh, babe.
His name will be Amir.
You have a daughter, right?
Yes.
Let's say it's her birthday.
Just humor me here, Sonny.
She wants to eat at her
favorite restaurant. Where's that?
Where?
Jensen's Steakhouse? McD's?
- We usually go to a place called Amigos.
- Okay.
You're on your way to Amigos.
You're in the car. She's so excited.
She's psyched,
because she's with her dad.
You arrive, open the door.
Bingo! Two seats left.
But you have your back to the door.
What now?
She's already sat down.
You can't sit anywhere else.
- What's the point of this?
- It's about paranoia. Anxiety.
Your mind is churning because
you've got your back to the door.
But she refuses to switch seats.
So, Sonny, what do you do?
Will you give your daughter
the birthday she deserves?
Then tell me,
what's her favorite color?
Sonny...
Just because you have a daughter
doesn't mean she has a dad.
We'll be here to support you.
But only you can give her
the dad she deserves.
Just a sec.
- Cairo!
- I told you not to touch me!
Hisham! Hey, hey, hey!
Relax.
Hey, hey. Calm down, Hisham!
Cool it!
Fuck.
Relax! Let's turn him over.
Three, two, one...
- Fuck you, you dog!
- Calm down.
- I'll fuck you up.
- Cool it, Hisham.
- This isn't doing you any good.
- Fuck you.
Everything under control?
Hisham?
- We're here for you.
- Fuck you, too. Fucking whore.
- Hisham, go cool down.
- Shut the fuck up!
Cool it. What about you two?
Are you two okay?
- Cairo, are you okay?
- Yeah. I just need a minute.
- Cairo?
- Yes.
- Everything okay?
- He spit in my face and broke my phone.
Don't worry, okay?
I'll get this fixed.
- It's my personal phone.
- Use your work phone in the meantime.
- So, do you want to press charges?
- No, he's just not ready.
- What about Sonny?
- Sonny is ready.
Nice work.
Whoa, Hamza's got himself a lady.
- Good thing they didn't get your chain.
- It's all I've got left from my dad.
- Remember to ice that eye, babe.
- Yeah, yeah. Relax.
- See you.
- Bye.
- Who's that?
- You scared me!
- Who is it?
- No one, just some girl.
- You want her? I've got four others.
- Get it together.
- What's that?
- I played soccer yesterday.
- Hamza, what is that? Seriously.
- Just playing soccer with the others.
You know how they are. Animals.
I got elbowed.
- Relax, it's nothing.
- You'll tell me if something's up?
- Of course.
- You're not getting into trouble?
- Relax, it's just a bruise.
- You know you can talk to me, right?
Good. What are you doing here?
I thought you were coming later.
- Grandma asked me to pick up some lamb.
- I'll take it. Come to dinner tonight.
- Wallah, I can't tonight.
- Why not?
- I've got stuff to do.
- Suddenly you're so important?
- I haven't seen you in four days.
- Two. Your math is terrible.
- Wait, isn't that Maryam?
- Yeah, I think so.
- It is. Go help her with her bags.
- What do you mean?
Show some manners. Be a gentleman.
Come on, yallah.
Go help her. She's alone.
Yallah, hurry up.
- Can I help?
- Thank you, habibi.
Anwar,
you can't just light up out here.
Leave me alone.
Let me dream myself back to Thailand.
Brother, just imagine waking up next to
two hookers every morning.
- Isn't Thailand full of trannies?
- Shut up.
It's true.
There are trannies in Thailand.
I'm just telling our brother here.
Is this your cousin?
Is this the kid whose dad
left him when he was little?
Is it him or not?
I'm asking you, brother.
- Where's your dad?
- What do you mean?
Where'd your dad go?
- Where would he be?
- It's a simple question.
What about your dad? The whole building
reeked of pussy when he came home.
At least my dad came home.
He worked at a fish shop.
- Where's your dad?
- Forget my dad, habibi.
- Call him.
- I'm not calling anyone.
- Anwar?
- Kamal.
Kamal. Get lost.
- Where's your dad? I'm talking to you.
- Shut up about my dad, habibi.
- I'll fuck you up.
- Anwar...
Did your dad at least teach you
to count to three?
Did he teach you?
Yallah, count.
Anwar...
Fucking idiot...
Keep your mouth shut next time.
He's a psychopath.
The goods have arrived.
You know the procedure?
- Same as always.
- Make it express.
The Serbs want their money fast.
I'll have two guys bagging up.
Kamal will pick up.
- Who's gonna bag up?
- The new guys.
- Why the new guys?
- Why not?
- I started out bagging myself.
- This is a lot of pounds.
I'll handle it.
Fine. It's your ass on the line
if something happens.
Zero?
Don't play dumb.
That's the last time you pull out a gun
when there are kids around.
Understand?
What are you saying,
you fucking bum?
That's enough.
Sort out the coke. No delays.
Yallah.
Get the fuck out of my car.
Was he shocked to hear you speak Arabic?
He was speechless.
So I just took my mint and left.
- Was the mint any good?
- No, because it wasn't Moroccan.
- It doesn't even have a smell.
- Moroccan mint is best.
- Exactly.
- Well done, Cille.
What about that eye of yours?
It looks pretty bad.
Relax. It's just me and the boys,
playing soccer. It's normal.
- Are you playing soccer, or...?
- Remember how I used to play?
- I'd come home looking just like that.
- No, babe, not like that.
I've threatened to go with him
if they don't stop.
- It'll fade in a few days.
- In no time.
Everything's fine.
They just need to learn to play nice.
You're all purple...
They've been behind the entire game,
but after a hopeless tackle by Acerbi...
Wallah, if they miss,
I'll burn my Milan jersey.
- I bet you they'll miss.
- He has to score.
If the keeper doesn't save,
he'll be thrashed in the locker room.
- Fuck!- Hamza!
- How could he miss?
- The keeper can't afford to miss.
- Fuck that. It's over anyway.
- Sick game, though.
- Will you get me a new Milan jersey?
- Weren't you going to burn yours?
- I've lost it.
- How did that happen?
- I just lost it.
- You didn't lose it.
There's some lady wearing it...
She can't hear us.
- What the hell?
- So, do you need an XS or XL?
Which lady is it for?
You need an XS or XL?
- Will you get your nephew a new jersey?
- Yes. And your ladies.
Just tell me how many ladies you've got.
Why won't you tell me these things?
I've gotta run, okay?
Need anything?
Yes, to know whether to buy XS or XL.
But you never tell me anything.
- Don't stay out late, Hamza.
- Yallah salaam!
- Yallah, Hamza!
- Who's there?
- It's just me.
- What are you doing?
What I'm doing? Why aren't you
picking up your fucking phone? Huh?
- Relax.
- Why aren't you picking up?
I don't give a fuck
if Saddam knew your dad.
Okay, fine. Got it.
What's that?
- You like it?
- That's serious business, wallah.
- Why not just a normal gun?
- Shut up. We've got work to do.
Yallah.
- Kamal.- Anwar, habibi.
- What's up, brother?- My girl just came by with a bottle.
- I'll pick up tomorrow instead.
- This can't wait, brother.
- Let me have a good time, man.
- Tomorrow morning at the latest.
I want that shit out of my apartment.
And don't drink too much, you drunk.
Good evening...
Fucking faggot.
Come on out.
Nice and easy.
- Don't take it off yet! Ready?
- So ready.
Go ahead.
- Welcome. It's all yours.
- That's not happening.
You have it all to yourself!
While you're here, it's yours.
Are those molehills where you buried
all the other people you help?
That's where I buried the people
out to get you.
The grand living room.
- What a fucking dump.
- It is what it is.
I've got your snacks. There's a fridge,
a TV. There are even stuffed owls.
You've got everything you need.
- You're taking my phone?
- Afraid so.
- Is there internet?
- No internet. People get desperate.
What the fuck am I meant to do?
Solve sudokus? Fuck that owl?
You could take a stroll in nature.
Or watch TV.
There's a Nintendo.
Let me just get this.
Just a second.
The Exit Program, this is Cairo.
Leyla? Leyla, what's going on?
What do you mean
he didn't come home last night?
Listen, sometimes he crashes
at a friend's place.
Hey, Leyla. Calm down.
Is his phone on?
It's off?
You haven't talked to him in a month?
Elias, be honest.
Are you covering for him because
he's with a girl? Tell me the truth.
He never usually turns his phone off.
He knows he's meant to call back.
We've called and called...
Let's take a deep breath.
How old is your son?
He's 16.
- When did you last see him?
- Yesterday.
- He hasn't even been gone for 24 hours?
- Didn't you hear me? He's 16.
- That's a long time to be missing...
- Leyla, easy.
Is there any reason to believe
he might be in danger?
- In danger? What are you talking about?
- Is he involved with anyone?
- Are you implying my son is a criminal?
- Leyla...
Leyla, please give me
a moment with them.
- I work for The Exit Program.
- Is the missing person your son?
He's my nephew,
and that's my brother's wife.
I know he hasn't been gone very long.
But I spoke to his best friend.
- It gave me a bad feeling.
- A feeling of what?
He's not picking up. People call him
at strange times. He acts weirdly.
- I'm afraid he's involved in something.
- Like you were at his age?
- Is there a problem?
- I have no problem.
Would you mind getting
your colleague to control himself?
Are you here to help, or what?
Listen, sometimes boys just
need a break from everything.
Give it another 24 hours, and if he
doesn't turn up, we'll start a search.
We've got to get going.
We'll be in touch. Salaam alaikum.
What the hell was that?
Why do we have to wait 24 hours?
We're not waiting.
- Salaam alaikum.
- Alaikum salaam.
What's up, habibi?
Can I help you?
What's up? What do you want?
I want to talk to him.
Congo.
Just let him in.
So, Machiavelli has returned.
- Did you get fed up with cop life?
- I'm not a cop.
A whore's a whore, brother.
- How are you?
- Cut the crap. What do you want?
- Hamza. Do you know where he is?
- Aren't you his uncle?
I'm assuming an uncle
would know something like that.
But you've come here.
After how many years?
Hamza is missing.
He hasn't come home.
No one knows where he is.
So let me know if you hear anything.
I haven't seen your face
in ten fucking years.
And this is the first thing
you say to me? Huh?
Huh, Cairo?
Fucking bitch.
Call me if you hear anything.
What's up, fucking pig?
Aren't you a pig?
Nice chain.
You looking for trouble?
What are you doing here? Yallah.
Eh?
See you, sweetheart.
Bye-bye.
Fucking pig.
What if I saw someone
wearing Hamza's chain?
You saw someone wearing his chain?
Cairo?
Are you there?
What's going on? What is it?
- I need to fucking find him, Vicky.- I know, Cairo.
- Did you tell the police?
- Fuck them. I need to find him now.
We're going to figure this out.
Deep breaths, Cairo.
I've got some contacts with the police
who may be able to help.
- What's up, Saddam?
- You having a nice time?
Stand up when I speak to you.
Where's Hamza?
What, cat got your tongue?
Weren't you with him a few days ago?
Yes. I sent him out for more bags.
He never came back.
- Just like that?
- Yeah, I had to send Zuz out after him.
Do I have to cut your tongue off?
Who is it you're talking to?
- Is the delivery under control?
- Yeah. It's at my place.
Why not at Kamal's?
He had important business.
Family matters.
Your ass is on the line if something
goes wrong. Sort out the delivery.
- The Serbs have busted my skull.
- Okay.
And find out where the fuck Hamza is.
Go look for him before I fuck you up.
Fuck Hamza.
ALL THE WAY UNTIL DEATH
The police are investigating
Why do we even bother?
No one here is ever willing to talk.
Maybe if you relaxed a little,
people would open up.
Take off your badge.
We look like cops from miles away.
Al-Ramari.
This is the police.
No one's home.
- Fuck.
- This is the police.
Could we have a word?
You smell that?
This is the police.
- You've reached the voicemail...
- This is the police.
- Should we kick in the door?
- Hell no.
- Salaam alaikum. Do you live here?
- Yes.
- Mind if we ask you a few questions?
- I need to pray.
You pray five times a day,
so maybe you can sit this one out.
It'll only take a moment.
- What's up, brother?
- Zuz, you asshole. Where are you?
- I'm out looking for Hamza. Why?
- Where is that fucking bum hiding?
I've called him a hundred times.
Is your whole family inbred?
Who knows.
I haven't seen him since yesterday.
Useless fucking junkie.
We're looking for this guy.
His name is Hamza.
- Have you seen him?
- He helped me with my bags.
- He helped you with your bags?
- It's very sad.
What's sad?
It's...
The gangs, doing criminal activities.
Gangs? Do you think they might be
involved in Hamza's disappearance?
I don't know,
but my son was killed by a gang.
I'm so sorry.
- Were you home Thursday evening?
- Yes.
Have you seen or heard anything
that might help us find Hamza?
I'm not certain, but I think I saw him
go into the apartment next door.
- Who? Hamza?
- Yes.
You saw Hamza next door
Thursday evening?
I'm not sure, but I think so.
- I don't want any trouble.
- You have nothing to worry about.
There's reasonable suspicion to kick
in that door. Thank you so much.
Close the door. Didn't your dad teach
you to close the door behind you?
Who are you?
What the fuck are you doing here?
Relax, bro.
Shut the fuck up. Get up.
Okay. Why so serious?
- I said, get up.
- Yeah?
Alright.
Then let's get up.
- What now?
- Yallah.
Stop. Don't turn around.
Take off the chain.
- Chain?
- Just fucking take it off.
You're hilarious.
All this for a chain?
Here you go, you junkie.
Take it.
- Go buy yourself a life with it.
- Yallah.
Hey! Open the door!
Fucking moron.
- Get me out of here.
- Shut the fuck up.
I'll fuck you up,
fucking idiot.
Wallah, I'm claustrophobic.
I'll fuck your face up.
- Stand up.
- You want to die?
- Where are we going? It's muddy.
- Stop talking. Turn right.
I'll fuck you to the right.
Look, my sandals are all fucking muddy.
What now?
Yallah.
What?
You want me to open the door for you?
Stand there, up against that.
Turn around.
- Arms up.
- Okay, I see. I knew it. Dirty.
What now?
Huh, big guy? Fuck you.
Are you done playing games?
Are you happy now?
Yeah?
- Where'd you get this?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Where did you get this?
- Fuck you.
- Fuck Hamza.
- Hey!
Choose your words carefully.
I'll ask again: Where did you get this?
Get your dirty hands off me.
Get them off me.
Okay. Fine.
- What are you gonna do now?
- Let's see how long you last.
Wallah, you piece of shit.
Fucking shit!
Come back!
I don't see anything right now,
but you will meet again.
He'll be back soon enough.
- Cairo, salaam alaikum.
- Alaikum salaam, Maryam.
- How are you?
- All right. And you?
I'm well.
Thank you for asking.
Do the police have any news?
They're doing what they can,
but they haven't found anything yet.
Anwar is missing.
What are you telling me?
Anwar.
We haven't heard from him since Sunday.
The coke?
Answer me.
It's gone.
- Cops?
- It doesn't seem like it.
- Did you check his apartment?
- Yeah.
We searched the whole place.
There was nothing.
24 hours, Kamal.
Or your mother will bury you.
Yallah.
All of you, get lost.
Amir! Saddam!
What the fuck are you doing?
Babe?
The nightmares again?
Allahu Akhbar...
- Where the fuck have you been?
- Listen, I get it.
I know guys like you
are loyal to the bone.
I respect it.
I know the street demands it.
But now I need some fucking information.
I'm not telling you shit. And I need
a shit. How long have I been here?
Yallah. Get up.
Go take a shit.
Undo these or pull my pants down
so I can shit.
Fucking turn around
and let me shit in peace!
Hamza is my nephew.
All of a sudden, he disappeared.
Just like that.
And suddenly you're walking around
wearing his chain.
So I'm going to ask you very calmly...
- Where did you find that chain?
- Let me just...
I'll ask you calmly just once:
Where did you find that chain?
I don't know where he is, man.
Fucking piece of shit.
Lift your arms.
Shut the fuck up
and tell me right now.
Where did you find Hamza's chain?
Where did you find his chain?
Where?
- Let me wipe my ass first.
- Fuck your ass! Where did you find it?
- Where?
- In the stairwell.
What the fuck was he doing
in your stairwell?
Chill the fuck out, man!
Get that out of my face.
What was he doing in your stairwell?
- I don't know.
- Sleep well.
Stop! Hey! Wait, wait.
Sofia. Sofia.
Sofia.
- Sofia who?
- The Serb's daughter. Her name's Sofia.
Maybe they found out
she and Hamza are together.
- What Serb? Dragan?
- Yes, Dragan!
Yallah, let me go. Enough.
You got what you wanted.
You can have more to eat
when you give me more information.
Come back! Cairo!
Fuck.
MISSING
Babe. Listen to me, okay?
This isn't your job to fix.
Okay?
I mean it.
Yeah.
- Come eat something.
- I'm coming.
I'm going to go put up posters
at the boxing club, okay?
I'm sure we'll find him.
This is Cairo.
Hey, brother...
- Saddam?- Who else would it be? Your dad?
Let's put our issues aside.
Is there any news about Hamza?
- Not yet.- Hmm...
One of my soldiers has gone missing too.
I think something is going on.
Cairo?
Do you still talk to Dragan?
Yallah.
We'll take mine.
- We'll take mine, habibi.
- I can't be seen in that.
Habibi, where's yours?
Are you fucking kidding me?
New car, huh?
- Are you still with Cille?
- Yeah, we're hanging in there.
- No kids?
- No kids.
So it doesn't work?
Balls too small?
Do you have a family now?
I have a daughter.
Isn't it time to consider retirement, then?
Retirement?
- Why the fuck would I retire?
- To spend time with your daughter.
What's her name?
- Her name is Hana.
- Hana?
- Yes.
- Beautiful name.
Do you know her favorite color?
Enough!
Drop the fucking nursery teacher talk.
Favorite color, schmavorite color.
Brother,
have you still got yours?
I'm not like you, a fucking bitch who
ran away. 'All The Way' forever. Traitor.
With or without you.
'All The Way Until Death'.
Cairo.
When we get inside,
I'll do the talking.
I'm serious. No going psycho like in
the old days. The Serbs don't kid around.
That's fine. Come on.
This way.
Give us a moment.
Problems with the delivery?
No.
What can I do for you, Saddam?
Some of our boys have disappeared.
Disappeared?
- You don't think it's...
- No.
Why?
Have you heard something?
People disappear like money
in the hands of a gambler.
You think I'm behind this?
- We think it's somebody...
- It's my nephew, Hamza.
He disappeared,
and he knows your daughter, Sofia.
Who?
I saw them together.
Dragan...
Who did you see?
Your daughter.
Hey! What are you doing?
Get the cleaver.
- Dragan...
- Dragan, what are you doing?
- Come here.
- Dragan! Dragan!
Wait. Wait...
- Dragan...
- Shut the fuck up!
I'm going to call her
and ask if she knows your nephew.
Be quiet.
- Hey, Papa.
- Hi, sweetheart. How are you?
- I'm fine.
- Do you know a boy by the name of...
Hamza.
- No. Why do you ask?
- Just answer, my darling.
No, I don't know anyone named Hamza.
Why do you ask?
- You don't know anyone by that name?- I told you, no.
Okay.
Sofia! This is Cairo.
Hamza has gone missing!
- Who's that?
- No one, darling.
- I want to see who it is.
- No, forget it.
I want to see who it is!
Stand up.
Sofia.
Sofia, Hamza's missing.
- If you know anything...- I've tried calling and texting him.
The last time I saw him, he got into a
fight with some racists from Vestegnen.
The two of us are going to talk
when I get home.
- Yes. Sorry, Papa.
- Bye.
Hey, you know how it is. Family.
Danilo...
Tell Cairo what you saw
in Vestegnen.
- I hope you find your nephew.
- Relax, brothers!
Hey, Saddam.
Don't forget my money.
I've run into some strange people
in Vestegnen lately.
Strange how?
Racists, bikers. The types
who don't like people like you.
Once, I heard them talk
about killing pakis.
I assumed they were baked,
but then I met their leader, Anker.
A full-blown psychopath.
One time,
I delivered a buzz saw to them.
- Where?
- Out in the sticks somewhere.
I don't remember exactly where,
but they were talking big about -
- butchering pigs,
that sort of thing.
Thanks. We'll check it out.
- It's Amir's son, right?
- Yeah.
When I saw him at the workshop,
he looked just like him.
I almost thought he was Amir.
What the fuck was he doing
at your workshop?
Saddam. Fucking answer me.
Don't fucking tell me
he was at your workshop.
Does he work for you?
- Does he, Saddam?
- What if he does?
- You fucking bum.
- What do you mean? Me?
Haven't you fucked up my family enough?
Where is he right now? Tell me,
before I take you down right here.
Easy...
Hey! Where's Amir, Cairo?
- Fuck you! Don't fucking touch me.
- Hey, get out of here.
Fuck you.
I'll find him by myself.
- Get lost.
- Stay away from me, you bum.
What the fuck?
Are you out of your mind?
- Control him, or I'll do it for you.
- Get your hands off me, Danilo.
- Fuck, man.
- Give me a ride.
Baba,
will you give me the other markers?
- All of them?
- Just the yellow, blue, and brown.
Brown is my favorite.
- It is?
- Yeah.
Will you be home tomorrow too?
Of course, Baba.
Anker Sørensen, Vestegnen.
Recruits at Amigos.
Goddammit, Sonny.
- The Exit Program, this is Cairo.- It's me. Where the fuck have you been?
I was under a lot of pressure.
- You didn't come home last night.
- I know, babe.
Cille?
Are you okay?
- I'm worried about you, babe.
- I'm fine.
You don't seem fine.
Listen to me.
If we're going to start a family,
you need to let me in.
You can't just shut down like that.
I thought we were better than this.
Cairo, I'm talking to you.
- Let's just get this over with.
- What do you mean "over with"?
- Don't make a scene.
- That was a fucked-up thing to say.
- Cille, there are other people here.
- I don't give a shit.
- Cecilie?
- Yes.
Sorry, brother.
Dragan wants the money you owe him.
I need more time, Danilo.
Just until next week.
You're already a week late.
You know how he is
when people shit on agreements.
The full sum today, Saddam.
I can't help you anymore.
They're back.
- I gave you 24 hours.
- Saddam, I looked all night.
I've been busting heads to make
people talk. No one knows anything.
He's gone.
Wallah, Saddam.
I went to see his dad and his brothers.
No one knows anything.
They haven't heard from him.
There's something
I've been wondering about.
Where were you?
What do you mean?
Weren't you supposed to
handle the pick-up?
Yeah, but I had a family emergency.
I had to be there.
- With your family?
- Yeah.
So why didn't you tell me?
Eh? Please tell me
your mama or baba almost died.
Then I'd understand.
Well?
Saddam, please.
Brother.
- Brother, huh? Zuz!
- Saddam?
- Come here, Zuz.
- Yes, brother.
Where was this little whore?
Have you suddenly gone mute?
Where was he?
- Where was he?
- He was with a girl.
A girl?
I'm about to start a war with the Serbs
just so you could see some girl.
Saddam, I'll fix this.
Just give me another 24 hours.
Saddam...
You're off fucking whores?
Are you?
I'll fuck you up,
you fucking pussy.
I'll fucking destroy you!
Fucking bitch!
You fucking pussy.
Zuz.
I have a job for you.
Let me just explain. I know this is
hard for you, but I'm also...
- What are you talking about?
- I'm trying to apologize!
- So be present.
- I'm physically present.
- I mean mentally present!
- My mind is all over the place.
Then talk to me about
what's going on, so I can help you.
- I've known you for 15 years!
- Babe, seriously...
Cairo,
do you know if Hamza knew this guy?
- No.
- Are you sure?
A witness saw Hamza enter his apartment
the night he disappeared.
- Hamza was with him that night?
- That's what we've been told.
You've been in there?
We searched his apartment,
but no one was there.
Ring any bells?
Wake up, you fucking asshole.
Wake up!
What is this I'm hearing?
You fucking jackal.
Hamza was in your apartment.
Seriously?
Why didn't you tell me?
- What are you talking about?
- What I'm talking about?
You understand me now?
No one can fucking find you out here.
I'll bury you out here,
and I'll take my time doing it.
Every fucking inch of your
disgusting body.
Do you fucking understand?
Do you? Talk.
Hamza was at my place.
We were bagging up.
I sent him out for more bags.
He never came back.
That's it, brother.
I swear that's all.
- What about the chain?
- I borrowed it from him before he left.
Are you lying to me?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Did you kill him?
Did you fucking kill Hamza?
Where's Hamza?
Where is he?
Sonny?
Sonny, it's me. Open up.
Sonny!
Sonny, open up!
Where the fuck have you been?
I've been here for a month!
Where the fuck were you?
You can't just fucking leave me!
Come on,
let's go inside and talk.
- Sonny, I need your help.
- My help?
I'm looking for a guy named Anker.
A racist from Vestegnen.
- What do you need Anker for?
- You know him?
- Yes, I know Anker. Do you?
- Do you have his address?
No.
I came here to get away from all that!
I told you.
I've already told you!
Shut the fuck up.
I want nothing to do with him.
I'm getting out of that shit.
- Fuck you, and fuck Exit!
- Shut the fuck up, okay!
When I ask for his address,
you fucking give it to me. You hear me?
Do you hear what I'm fucking saying?
Don't play dumb with me.
Give me his address,
and then shut the fuck up.
Sit down.
Give me his fucking address right now.
Good morning, paki.
You awake?
You awake? Or are you just trying
to avoid paying rent?
- Get him up.
- Hey, hey, hey...
- What's up? Good morning.
- Up you go.
I'm not looking for trouble.
Calm down.
- Then what are you doing here?
- With this, sniffing around my backyard?
- Relax. I'm looking for my nephew.
- Who's your nephew?
16 years old. Short hair.
Has a scar by his...
- Is it the guy in the soccer jersey?
- Where's my nephew?
- The guy we thrashed at the station?
- Do you know where he is?
I'll fucking crush you!
You little bitch.
You think you're so tough? Little bitch.
You're fucking toast.
Is anyone else coming? Answer me!
- There's no one else.
- Give him what his nephew got.
- Come on!
- Get him up. Come on.
Who sent you? Huh?
Huh? Answer me! Fuck you!
- What the fuck is going on?- The fucking paki shot me!
Who the fuck are you?
This looks cozy.
Where's my invite?
- Shut up, you fucking ape.
- I'll shove this up your ass.
That ape is coming with me.
Yallah, Zero.
Go get him.
What's up?
Piss off!
Congo, go help him.
Just stay where you are, little friend,
and no one gets hurt.
Tough guy, huh?
Who are you spitting at?
Hey, Cairo.
Give your fucking car keys to Zero.
You're fucking lucky Zuz followed you.
- Fuck, man!
- What do you want?
Fucking paki! Bring it on.
You've got nothing.
Congo...
Get into your car.
Fuck!
Take a shower, freshen up.
Go home to your family.
Call me if you need anything, okay?
No. 4 Hindbærvænget.
- That's where Anwar is.
- What?
What the fuck are you saying?
Yallah, Zero.
Did you get the address?
Anwar.
You awake?
My brother.
What's up, bro?
Are we bouncing?
Should we get moving?
Did you hit your head or something?
Hey, Anwar. Wake up.
- Where's the coke?
- Wallah, I'm sorry, brother.
Sorry about what?
- Where's the coke, Anwar?
- Wallah, brother. The cops came.
The cops came.
Don't tell me the cops took the coke.
You know me, brother.
Of course not. I hid it.
The man hid the coke.
Yallah.
Congo, get him out of here.
Let's get out of this rathole.
- Congo, I've missed you.
- I've missed you too, brother.
Open it.
It's Christmas morning for Daddy, huh?
- You got off lucky.
- I told you, bro.
We're all good. Bring the bag
and let's move, shababs.
The streets are gonna be snowy tonight.
Amir!
Yeah, bro?
I've been wondering...
Who the fuck shows up
with a grenade like that?
Bro...
I saved it for a special occasion. It
finally came, thanks to your ugly face.
Wallah, you delivered 100%.
Fucking 100%.
Thanks for saving my ass today.
Fuck off with that sentimental shit.
What's wrong with you?
How's your brother?
- Abbas?
- Yeah.
He's busy. Malmö is booming.
Nothing like here in Nørrebro.
As long as you've still got each other.
That's all that matters.
- How's the family?
- Total chaos.
I don't know what to say.
Nørrebro isn't like it used to be.
There's no place like Nørrebro.
It's home, sweet home, bro.
- Stop it.- But it's true.
They've wrecked the place
with all this renovation.
- Remember Nørrebro in our day?- Yeah...
All that's left is Divan Kebab.
Number 26 with Thousand Island.
If they close, bro,
I'm out of here too.
By the way...
I was thinking about something.
How would it work if I decided
to try out that fucking retirement?
Then you'd tell us,
and we'd figure it out.
No stress.
If that's what you want,
we'll work it out together.
Yeah, okay.
Have you still not gotten
hold of those fucking Serbs?
Now the coke's ready,
and they don't pick up the phone.
Let's give it fifteen minutes, then
we'll go tell them we're ready to go.
- Get down!
- He's in the car!
Get him in the car. Yallah!
Get him in.
- Yallah, get in.
- Fuck those Serbs!
Good thing you finally
got your phone back.
Don't you think it might be good
for you to start working again soon?
Don't you?
Maybe. I don't know.
I think it would be a good idea.
Cille, I'm saying maybe.
I don't know.
Welcome to voicemail.
You have five new messages.
To listen to your messages,
press one.
First new message.
Received two days ago at 12:52 PM.
Uncle? It's me, Hamza.
I'm begging you. Please help me.
I'm supposed to tell you to...
Who are you? Where is Hamza?
You've got until midnight.
Otherwise Hamza dies.
- What's the matter?- I need your help, Vicki.
Vicki, can you trace a number?
- I need you to trace it immediately.
- It could take a few days. Why?
It's about Hamza. And it's an emergency.
Find out where the SIM comes from.
- And who owns it.
- I'll see what I can do.
Why are we watching
corner shop surveillance tapes?
The provider that the number belongs to
only has three retailers in the country.
One of them is that corner shop and
Hamza lives 300 yards down the street.
Okay, but what are we looking for?
This is going to take hours.
Cairo, I'm having them look through
the tapes from that corner shop.
We have no idea what
we're looking for, but...
We've just got to stay calm.
This will take some time.
- Hey, bro. What's up?
- What are you up to?
Just taking care of some business.
What's going on?
Hamza's alive. I need your help.
What do you mean?
Cairo, where are you?
- The tunnel.- Yallah, I'm coming.
What's up?
- Hey, brother.
- Where's Hamza?
- What's with the vest?
- What do you care? Where's Hamza?
- Why the fuck are you wearing a vest?
- Is this a fucking therapy session?
- I don't fucking have time for this.
- Aren't you fucking tired of all this?
All these years. Aren't you tired
of constantly being on guard?
Of not being able to take your family
to the playground without fear?
Who the fuck kidnapped Anwar?
Who the fuck made this mess I'm in?
There's been nothing but trouble
since you came back, Cairo.
That's why I'm wearing a fucking
bulletproof vest. Because of you.
Don't forget where we fucking come from.
Maybe you've made a nice,
peaceful life for yourself.
Brother, look at you.
You've turned the whole city upside down
trying to find your nephew.
You're still the same Cairo.
Just wrapped up in fancy paper.
You fucking bum.
Fucking idiot.
And you're blind, brother.
Drop this and come with me.
Saddam, I'll tell you once.
Fucking stop this.
Don't give me that moralizing bullshit.
I wasn't the one who turned my back
on everyone.
I lost my brother that night.
My fucking brother.
That night,
I lost both my brothers.
Understand?
What the fuck are we doing here?
Yallah, where's Hamza?
Where is he?
Why did you bring me here?
To reminisce about the old days?
2 hours left
"All The Way until death", huh?
Uncle? It's me, Hamza.
I'm begging you. Please help me.
I'm supposed to tell you...
... to kill Saddam.
I'm going to get killed.
Send a video once you've done it.
Then you'll get the address.
22 Lundtoftegade, 2. th
Come alone
Hey...
- Finally someone we know.
- What?
There. Rewind a little.
What was the name again?
Maryam, what am I doing here?
Why do I have a message
with your address?
Do you feel my pain?
I feel your pain.
When your child doesn't come home.
I feel for you.
That feeling.
My heart is burned
after what happened to my son.
Look at the pain around you.
Don't you think I know
you were the ones who killed my son?
- My Younes was an innocent boy.
- No, no, no, Maryam.
- Where is Hamza?
- You killed him.
- You killed my son.
- Maryam, where is Hamza?
You killed my son.
Maryam.
Hamza!
Hamza! Hamza!
Where is he?
Where is Hamza, Maryam?
He was in the stairwell.
With that man, the criminal.
I asked him for help with my sofa.
I needed to move it.
Maryam, I'm serious.
Where is he?
Hamza is a good boy.
Enough, Maryam.
I can't lose him.
You and your friend Saddam
are like cancer in my body.
You poison the youth.
The children of parents.
I still see my son in my dreams.
Do you understand?
- You killed my son, the two of you.
- I'm sorry, Maryam. For everything.
- Why are you upset? I lost my son.
- I'm sorry for all we did.
- Did you know he was my only child?
- Please, tell me where Hamza is.
I can't lose him.
I lost my son!
I lost my only son!
And here you are, on your knees.
What are you begging for?
I can't lose him.
He's in the sofa.
Hamza!
Hamza! Wake up!
Can you hear me?
Maryam...
I feel sorry for your mother.
For what she will now suffer.
It's the police!
Drop what's in your hands!
I repeat, drop what's in your hands!
Cairo?
Cairo!
I repeat, 22 Lundtoftegade.
Who's that in the car?
Abbas. From Malmö.
Saddam's brother.